LAUGHING MAN FANSUBS
Angels and demons were circling over me,
Crossing a brambly path of stars and milky ways.
He who does not perceive his calling,
does not know true happiness.
Watch in awe! Watch in awe!
Flying in glory, Flying in glory
I am calling, calling now.
Spirits rise and falling.
To be with you longer
Calling, calling...
in the depth of longing
To stay myself longer
The flow may swallow you, flying in glory
Enhanced patrols, eh?
Beyond
Good and Evil
Ishikawa, is there any new testimony
from the remaining assault team members?
Nothing too enlightening.
All we know is that they reported to Chief
Niimi, who recently committed cyberbrain suicide.
We haven't made any further
progress on that front.
Furthermore, the Laughing Man, who is
crucial to our case, is nowhere to be found.
True.
From now on, we will follow the Chief's orders
and go after this person.
This guy?!
Yes. Councilman Yakushima Kaoru, the current
Secretary General for the ruling coalition party.
Secretary General Yakushima is said
to be the number one power broker.
He was the Minister of Health and Welfare
when the first Laughing Man incident occurred.
He secured his current position of power by
transferring jurisdiction over cybernetic technology
from the Ministry of International Trade and Industry
to the Ministry of Health and Welfare.
He's a hardcore health and welfare faction member.
In addition, while this is not widely known,
he has strong ties with the MSDF.
Then that would explain where
that armour suit came from, right?
That's what the Chief seems to think, at least.
In truth, the connections between the
MSDF and politics were established
when Yakushima, a former MSDF admiral,
entered politics with substantial funding.
At that time, a MSDF accounting
official indicted Yakushima
of misappropriating secret funds for his own use.
However, the prosecutor in charge of
the case was found run over by a train
and the investigation was halted.
The case remained unsolved and the
charges against Yakushima were dropped.
In addition,
Daidou, the retired Police Commissioner,
was Yakushima's underclassman at
the National Defence Academy and
Imakurusu was one of Yakushima's closest
golf acquaintances since his days as a medic.
Are you sure you should be up and about?
I can't be resting at a time like this.
So in other words, he has enough political backing
to have been the person pulling the strings
behind the scenes in all of these cases.
Yes, although there is no proof at the moment.
How do you intend to go after a
Secretary General who is still in office?
We will investigate the last remaining connection between
Secretary General Yakushima and the Laughing Man Case.
SERANO Genomix.
Yes. The deliberate rejection of the Murai Vaccine, which
is thought to have instigated the Laughing Man Case,
and the concurrent acceptance of
Serano's micromachine treatment.
If we take custody of Ernest SERANO, who is thought
to have been deeply involved in both of these events,
and immediately conduct an interrogation,
then we should be able to gain insight into the
connection between Yakushima and the Laughing Man case.
Mr. SERANO has been under house arrest
for these six years since the incident
under the pretext of personal protection.
Do whatever it takes.
Place him under custody without fail.
The Laughing Man must have the same idea.
If we happen to run into each other, then what?
Place him under custody,
for in a sense, he is the single
most important witness in this case.
What about the possibility
that SERANO will be eliminated
as a result of our taking action yet again?
That is of course possible.
That's why you must succeed
no matter what the cost!
Mr. President, you have an incoming
transmission from the Netherlands branch.
What would you like me to do?
Please tell him that I will contact
him after I arrive in my office.
Understood, sir.
I apologise for always making
you act like my secretary.
Even so, you are the most competent detective
out of all the ones who
have been with me thus far.
How about actually becoming my secretary?
I'll pay you a comfortable salary.
Thank you for the kind offer.
It seems that your ride has arrived.
I see. Thank you.
I will be there shortly to escort
you, so please wait a moment.
I'm slightly nervous now that security
has been upped by another notch.
There is no need for you to be concerned.
The door's open.
From the time I saw the news about the
Sunflower Society and Imakurusu on TV,
I was prepared for the fact
that you would come here next.
I came here to have you fulfil the
promise you made to me six years ago.
Will you please come with me?
Subject has exited his quarters.
He is heading towards the entrance hall.
Good morning, sir.
Good morning.
Open the entrance doors.
Please be careful, sir.
Thank you.
Subject has exited the entrance hall.
Roger.
Confirmed exit.
It's the same thing that
happened the last time, isn't it?
Yes, the only difference this time is that there were
detectives in the hallways instead of your family members.
There were no cars following us, either.
Well, what now?
Let's see...
Sir, please turn left at the next light.
That's unusual.
Don't let them out of your sight!
With this, we have approximately
one hour before the unmarked
patrol car arrives at the
main SERANO Genomix branch.
Please tell me the reasons why
you did not keep the promise
you made to me and instead,
kept your silence for six years.
We have to decide on our plan of action.
How audacious of you.
BUS STOP
Don't move!
Put both hands on top of the car!
Don't panic.
We are from Section 9.
We contacted you in advance.
Is it true that Mr. SERANO
has already left the premises?
As usual, he left in his car. What about it?
Check the time.
Is that "as usual"?
What a diligent president.
You idiots all had your eyes stolen!
Mr. SERANO was alone even when I
told him that his car had arrived.
The security camera system's AI has been hacked.
"Medusa"?
Hand over your ID.
What?
Hurry up.
Shinhama Prefectural Police
Ishizawa Naoyuki
SECTION 1
Sheesh, you guys are all softies.
This is...?
There are interceptors.
To think that you guys are
still rigged with them...
Interceptors utilise a transmission device
within the cyberbrain when they relay data.
You would have occasionally felt
a heavy system load at those times.
What is going on...?
While your cyberbrains recorded
that only Mr. SERANO passed by,
the interceptors clearly show the Laughing Man.
This is the truth behind the
kidnapping six years ago.
Major, dive into all the IR Systems within a
three kilometre radius of the SERANO residence
and search for Mr. Serano's vehicle.
The Laughing Man has kidnapped Mr. SERANO again!
Find him, no matter what!
Roger.
However, there is no guarantee that
the car will be on the IR system.
Ishikawa!
I've been listening.
I'll run a complete search.
Factor in the possibility that
the AIs have been overwritten.
Roger.
Loiter around for about thirty minutes.
I have a personal matter to attend to.
Let's go.
The view from here has certainly changed a lot.
SERANO-San, you're starting
to get grey hairs, too.
These six years have been harsh.
While the pretext was to protect me
from receiving further threats from you,
in actuality, it was to keep an eye on me to ensure that
I would not reveal the truth behind the kidnapping.
For all intents and purposes, it was house arrest.
As for you, you seem to have lost
the naivete of six years ago.
Perhaps I have gained somewhat in maturity.
At the time, I was naive enough to really think about
striking down all the injustices in the world.
Even though you say that now,
you were a pretty passionate man
yourself, SERANO-San.
After all, even though your cyberbrain was infiltrated,
you kept company with an anonymous student,
who hacked into your
cyberbrain, for two whole days.
Back then, I had enough energy
to try and use logic to defeat
a student who spouted naivete.
2024 Japan International Expo
Awaji Expo
100 Days Until Opening
I understand your point,
but I'm a developer of a micromachine company,
not a member of the Drug Evaluation Committee!
I'm not involved with the rejection
of the Murai Vaccine in any way!
I know that.
However, the Drug Evaluation Committee
is a group of liars who are full of shit!
I will probably have to
challenge that group, but first,
I would like for you to publicize the fact that your company's
micromachines have nearly no effect on cyberbrain sclerosis!
As I've repeatedly told you
before, that is unacceptable!
As was written in an e-mail
threat three years earlier,
the micromachine treatment was only
a theoretical idea at the time!
But patents are like that!
It is in no way illegal to preemptively patent a
technology that one will attain with certainty!
That's what all the shitty lawyers say! Christ!
I do realise that my request
for approval was premature.
It was also a bluff aimed towards my competitors.
However, I believe that the treatment exceeded our expectations
and was approved by the Evaluation Committee after three months
because our theories were admittedly superior.
You have no idea how much damage there will be now
if we undermine faith in medical micromachines.
For the technology to substantially
develop in the years to come-
What I wish to say
is that it is a matter of life and death for
those who are suffering from cyberbrain sclerosis!
Couldn't you at least allow the
Murai Vaccine to have a chance
until micromachine treatment is
seen to have concrete effects?
There is nothing I can do
regarding the Murai Vaccine.
Are you really sure about that?
If God felt whimsical and
gave you cyberbrain sclerosis,
then would you choose micromachine
treatment without hesitation?
Of course.
I have pride and full confidence
in what I have created.
Then, what if your child became
inflicted with cyberbrain sclerosis?
Yes... it would be the same thing.
I cannot entertain hypothetical scenarios any further.
Pride and sentiments are different
things, aren't they...?
You're being unfair, SERANO-San.
If you have that much pride
in micromachine treatment,
then you should use your
position and enact justice!
Imakurusu only thought about rejecting the vaccine,
which had Dr. Murai's name attached to it!
The Evaluation Committee is a shit organisation
that was originally intended to just
stamp approval on new drugs that made it
through the Ministry of Health and Welfare!
Imakurusu, who became the Committee's director,
went through the trouble of making a stamp for
rejection just to destroy the Murai Vaccine!
your micromachines were
used in that ugly conflict!
Even you can't claim complete ignorance
about the circumstances involved, SERANO-San.
It didn't matter to them whether
it was your micromachines or not!
As long as the approval had been requested at that
time, it could have been any shit micromachine!
Fully aware that the health
industry is full of shit,
can you still say that it doesn't
have anything to do with you?!
Fine, let's do this.
For now, release me and let me be free again.
Afterward, I will gather the media
as soon as preparations are complete,
and announce the true status of
micromachine treatment as of now.
Will you really do that?
It is a promise that would
not benefit you in any way.
I'm not that stingy.
Although not to the same extent as you, I believe
I do have a certain sense of social justice.
I wonder about that...
I promise.
At the time, I was weary
from cyberbrain infiltration.
I made the promise out of
desperation; just to get out of there.
I also thought that you would
not make any further rash moves
once we were under public scrutiny
in front of the TV cameras.
Yes... unfortunately, however,
there was a S&W Chief's Special in my pocket.
Can you release me from cyberbrain infiltration?
You must know that this is a crime.
If you wish to hide your face
and maintain your anonymity,
then it wouldn't be a good
idea to appear on TV, would it?
It was fun debating with you.
But as one who must protect his company,
I may not be able to keep my promise.
Society is not as simplistic as you think it is.
I will not try to find out who you are, either.
For now, let's part our ways.
That is unfair of you!
This Morning's
Weather
Now tell the truth in front of the cameras!
Stop this. You aren't capable of shooting me.
Oh, do you think so?!
Afterward, when I was taken into
protective custody by the police,
my executive manager told me that my two days with you
had developed into a serious kidnapping incident,
which was causing a stir amongst the public.
Also, the moment after I left my home with you,
a massive ransom demand had
already been made to the company.
However, I couldn't bring myself to
believe that you had made such a demand.
You were indeed a hacking genius and a criminal,
but it seemed to me that you only
used your talents to confront all
the injustices in this world with
your youthful sense of justice.
However, the police decided that you
were a kidnapper after ransom money
and repeatedly interrogated me as to whether
I had any idea regarding your identity.
In spite of that, the managing executive and I
decided to maintain that we had no idea whatsoever
because we could not afford to have the inadequacies
of our company's micromachines questioned.
It was as you said;
I was painfully reminded of our guilty conscience,
that ransom was being demanded for hiding
the secret behind our micromachines.
And then, a killer virus later made its way
into your micromachines in another incident.
Yes. In addition to being angry at myself, who felt
elated upon approval of the micromachine treatment,
I cursed you from the bottom of my heart.
I thought, "This is just corporate terrorism,"
but it wasn't by you.
The evil that lurks in this world exists to a
far greater extent than we can possibly imagine.
You must know about the fact that public
funds were used to aid corporations
that were forced to the brink of
bankruptcy by the killer virus terrorism.
I will tell you about what
transpired after that as well.
At the same time as our stocks began
to recover from hitting rock-bottom,
a man claiming to be a member of a certain representative's
private support organisation appeared before us.
He said that he knew someone who could
put an end to corporate terrorism
and asked us to contribute
funding to the representative
in the event that an end to
the crimes was duly announced.
The presented amount was the
sum of the public funding we
received and the ransom money
that was previously demanded.
There was nothing to be surprised about;
as a latecomer in the industry, we were targeted
for corporate terrorism from the very beginning.
In other words, what I did was a truly
convenient performance for those people.
That seems to have been the case.
By mimicking what you did, they created an
illusory figure called the Laughing Man.
And by intermittently suggesting the
presence of a nonexistent criminal,
they manipulated stock prices and stole
money from other corporations as well.
Even before all of this happened,
I'm sure that they pocketed
a considerable amount of
profit by short selling stocks.
Was that representative the current
Secretary General Yakushima?
You knew?
After all, hackers originally existed for the
sole purpose of peeking at things that are hidden.
However, after being defeated by the depths of evil that
I saw in the abode of the demons I sought to challenge,
I also had no choice but to avert my eyes from everything and
maintain silence while turning a deaf ear to everything.
Just as you have done for the past six years.
"The Laughing Man"...
an ingenious nickname, isn't it?
I was only trying to quote Holden's words and
intended to disappear if I failed to persuade you,
but now it's merely a connection
with Salinger... geez.
Say, Serrano-San, if that's what they have done,
then I must become the original Laughing Man
and expose their fraud to the light of day!
I have also made my decision,
now that I have been able to see you again.
While there is little evidence to successfully indict
him, I will become one of your mimickers and fight.
Please stay alive until you
appear on the witness stand.
I will.
Squad Two in position!
Squad Three in position.
Squad Four in position!
All squads are now in position.
Building's security systems
are now under control.
Batou?
No changes perceived in targets.
Go in!
GOODS ENTRANCE
No one move!
Everyone stay where you are!
Secured target B.
He is alone.
There is no sign of target A.
Remain on standby.
It was quite some acting you did there.
With that, you could steal anyone's eye.
I've never been in any school plays, actually.
You were able to find the connection between
SERANO and that Yakushima guy, weren't you?
Yes.
What the Laughing Man told me was true as well.
With this, Mr. SERANO must
have hardened his resolve.
We can do this!
She's so cold and human
It's something humans do
She stays so cold in her soul, she's so number 9
She's incredible math
Just incredible math
And is she really human?
She says there's something new
But wake a lithium flower, just about to bloom
I smell lithium now
Smelling lithium now
How... is she what she doesn't say
She doesn't say
How is she when she doesn't suffer
I wonder what she does when she wakes up
When she wakes up